code:	category
1100:	"Chief executives, senior officials and legislators"
1110:	 Legislators and senior officials
1120:	Managing directors and chief executives
1200:	Administrative and commercial managers
1210:	Business services and administration managers
1220:	"Sales, marketing and development managers"
1300:	Production and specialized services managers
1310:	"Production managers in agriculture, forestry and fisheries"
1320:	"Manufacturing, mining, construction, and distribution managers"
1330:	Information and communications technology service managers
1340:	Professional services managers
1400:	"Hospitality, retail and other services managers"
1410:	Hotel and restaurant managers
1420:	Retail and wholesale trade managers
1430:	Other services managers
2100:	Science and engineering professionals
2110:	Physical and earth science professionals
2120:	"Mathematicians, actuaries and statisticians"
2130:	Life science professionals
2140:	Engineering professionals (excluding electrotechnology)
2150:	Electrotechnology engineers
2160:	"Architects, planners, surveyors and designers"
2200:	Health professionals
2210:	Medical doctors
2220:	Nursing and midwifery professionals
2230:	Traditional and complementary medicine professionals
2240:	Paramedical practitioners
2250:	veterinarians
2260:	Other health professionals
2270:	Assistant professionals
2300:	Teaching professionals
2310:	University and higher education teachers
2320:	Vocational education teachers
2330:	Secondary education teachers
2340:	Primary school and early childhood teachers
2350:	Other teaching professionals
2400:	Business and administration professionals
2410:	Finance professionals
2420:	Administration professionals
2430:	"Sales, marketing and public relations professionals"
2500:	Information and communications technology professionals
2510:	Software and applications developers and analysts
2520:	Database and network professionals
2600:	"Legal, social and cultural professionals"
2610:	Legal professionals
2620:	"Librarians, archivists and curators"
2630:	Social and religious professionals
2640:	"Authors, journalists and linguists"
2650:	Creative and performing artists
3100:	Science and engineering associate professionals
3110:	Physical and engineering science technicians
3120:	"Mining, manufacturing and construction supervisors"
3130:	Process control technicians
3140:	Life science technicians and related associate professionals
3150:	Ship and aircraft controllers and technicians
3200:	Health associate professionals
3210:	Medical and pharmaceutical technicians
3220:	Nursing and midwifery associate professionals
3230:	Traditional and complementary medicine associate professionals
3240:	Veterinary technicians and assistants
3250:	Other health associate professionals
3300:	Business and administration associate professionals
3310:	Financial and mathematical associate professionals
3320:	Sales and purchasing agents and brokers
3330:	Business services agents
3340:	Administrative and specialized secretaries
3350:	Regulatory government associate professionals
3400:	"Legal, social, cultural and related associate professionals"
3410:	"Legal, social and religious associate professionals"
3420:	Sports and fitness workers
3430:	"Artistic, cultural and culinary associate professionals"
3500:	Information and communications technicians
3510:	Information and communications technology operations and user support technicians
3520:	Telecommunications and broadcasting technicians
4100:	General and keyboard clerks
4110:	General office clerks
4120:	Secretaries (general)
4130:	Keyboard operators
4200:	Customer services clerks
4210:	"Tellers, money collectors and related clerks"
4220:	Client information workers
4300:	Numerical and material recording clerks
4310:	Numerical clerks
4320:	Material-recording and transport clerks
4400:	Other clerical support workers
4410:	Other clerical support workers
5100:	Personal service workers
5110:	"Travel attendants, conductors and guides"
5120:	cooks
5130:	Waiters and bartenders
5140:	"Hairdressers, beauticians and related workers"
5150:	Building and housekeeping supervisors
5160:	Other personal services workers
5200:	Sales workers
5210:	Street and market salespersons
5220:	Shop salespersons
5230:	Cashiers and ticket clerks
5240:	Other sales workers
5300:	Personal care workers
5310:	Child care workers and teachers' aides
5320:	Personal care workers in health services
5400:	Protective services workers
5410:	Protective services workers
6100:	Market-oriented skilled agricultural workers
6110:	Market gardeners and crop growers
6120:	Animal producers
6130:	Mixed crop and animal producers
6200:	"Market-oriented skilled forestry, fishery and hunting workers"
6210:	Forestry and related workers
6220:	"Fishery workers, hunters and trappers"
6300:	"Subsistence farmers, fishers, hunters and gatherers"
6310:	Subsistence crop farmers
6320:	Subsistence livestock farmers
6330:	Subsistence mixed crop and livestock farmers
6340:	"Subsistence fishers, hunters, trappers and gatherers"
7100:	"Building and related trades workers, excluding electricians"
7110:	Building frame and related trades workers
7120:	Building finishers and related trades workers
7130:	"Painters, building structure cleaners and related trades workers"
7200:	"Metal, machinery and related trades workers"
7210:	"Sheet and structural metal workers, moulders and welders, and related workers"
7220:	"Blacksmiths, toolmakers and related trades workers"
7230:	Machinery mechanics and repairers
7300:	Handicraft and printing workers
7310:	Handicraft workers
7320:	Printing trades workers
7400:	Electrical and electronic trades workers
7410:	Electrical equipment installers and repairers
7420:	Electronics and telecommunications installers and repairers
7500:	"Food processing, wood working, garment and other craft and related trades workers"
7510:	Food processing and related trades workers
7520:	"Wood treaters, cabinet-makers and related trades workers"
7530:	Garment and related trades workers
7540:	Other craft and related workers
8100:	Stationary plant and machine operators
8110:	Mining and mineral processing plant operators
8120:	Metal processing and finishing plant operators
8130:	Chemical and photographic products plant and machine operators
8140:	"Rubber, plastic and paper products machine operators"
8150:	"Textile, fur and leather products machine operators"
8160:	Food and related products machine operators
8170:	Wood processing and papermaking plant operators
8180:	Other stationary plant and machine operators
8200:	assemblers
8210:	assemblers
8300:	Drivers and mobile plant operators
8310:	Locomotive engine drivers and related workers
8320:	"Car, van and motorcycle drivers"
8330:	Heavy truck and bus drivers
8340:	Mobile plant operators
9100:	Cleaners and helpers
9110:	"Domestic, hotel and office cleaners and helpers"
9120:	"Vehicle, window, laundry and other hand cleaning workers"
9200:	"Agricultural, forestry and fishery labourers"
9210:	"Agricultural, forestry and fishery labourers"
9300:	"Labourers in mining, construction, manufacturing and transport"
9310:	Mining and construction labourers
9320:	Manufacturing labourers
9330:	Transport and storage labourers
9400:	Food preparation assistants
9410:	Food preparation assistants
9500:	Street and related sales and service workers
9510:	Street and related service workers
9520:	Street vendors (excluding food)
9600:	Refuse workers and other elementary workers
9610:	Refuse workers
9620:	Other elementary workers
10100:	Commissioned armed forces officers
10110:	Commissioned armed forces officers
10200:	Non-commissioned armed forces officers
10210:	Non-commissioned armed forces officers
10300:	"Armed forces occupations, other ranks"
10310:	"Armed forces occupations, other ranks"
